George Gaylord Simpson Papers 1918-1984 Mss.Ms.Coll.31
American Philosophical Society
- George Gaylord Simpson Papers
  - Series I. Correspondence, 1925-1984; 36 linear feet (Box 1-73)
    - Conniff, James C.G., 1946 (Box 15)
    - Conrad, Ernie, 1976 (Box 15)
    - Conseil de Direction, 1965 (Box 15)
    - Consolidated Book Publishers, 1970 (Box 15)
    - Continental Hotel, 1940 (Box 15)
    - Contreras, Julio R., 1975 (Box 15)
    - Contwell, R.J. (Mitch), 1969 (Box 15)
    - Converse College, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Cook, Harold J., 1928, 32-33, 36, 42, 58 (Box 15)
    - Cook, Susan, 1963 (Box 15)
    - Cook, Thos. & Son, 1967 (Box 15)
    - Cooke, Basil S., 1963, 67, 81 (Box 15)
    - Cooke, C. Wythe, 1941 (Box 15)
    - Cooke, H.B.S., 1958-67 (Box 15)
    - Cooke, Susan Byrne, 1966 (Box 15)
    - Cooney, Merle Andrew, 1961 (Box 15)
    - Cooper, Andrew, 1969 (Box 15)
    - Cooper, Barbara J., 1969 (Box 15)
    - Cooper, C. Forster, 1929, 37, 47 (Box 15)
    - Cooper, E.L., 1984 (Box 15)
    - Cooper, G. Arthur, 1966 (Box 15)
    - Cooper, John M., 1941 (Box 15)
    - Cooper, Margaret W., 1941 (Box 15)
    - Cooper, R.J., 1971 (Box 15)
    - Cooper, Terry J., 1973 (Box 15)
    - Cooperman, Maxine, 1973 (Box 15)
    - Coopernail, George P., 1934 (Box 15)
    - Coordination Universelle de la Bonne Volonte, 1948-64 (Box 15)
    - Copeland, Herbert F., 1964 (Box 16)
    - Coppenhaver, Dorian, 1975 (Box 16)
    - Corbeiller, Jean de, 1966 (Box 16)
    - Corbett, Paul, 1971-73 (Box 16)
    - Core, Earl L., 1955 (Box 16)
    - Corliss, John O., 1961, 64, 69-72, 78 (Box 16)
    - Cornell University (lecture), 1949 (Box 16)
    - Cornell University Press, 1980 (Box 16)
    - Corner, George W., 1955, 68, 71, 73, 76-78, 80 (Box 16)
    - Corning, Peter A., 1979-80 (Box 16)
    - Corro, Guillermo del, 1970-71 (Box 16)
    - Corson, D.D., 1974 (Box 16)
    - Corson, David W., 1975-77 (Box 16)
    - Corwin, James F., 1959 (Box 16)
    - Coryell, Roland S., 1962 (Box 16)
    - Coryndon, Shirley C., 1964-65, 67 (Box 16)
    - Cosmos Club, 1960-63, 74 (Box 16)
    - Costanzo, Joseph B., 1960 (Box 16)
    - Cotreau, Denis, 1966 (Box 16)
    - Cotterrell, Kathryn, 1974 (Box 16)
    - Cotton, E.L., 1933 (Box 16)
      Schoolteacher
    - Cottrell, G.W., 1947 (Box 16)
    - Coulon, Pierre de, 1952, 55 (Box 16)
    - Count, Earl W., 1954 (Box 16)
    - Couto, Carlos de Paula (Paula Couto), 1953-55, 57, 59-65, 68-70, 77, 79-84 (Box 16)
    - Couturier, M. (Marcel), 1950-1973; 34.0 Item(s) (Box 16)
      Biographical and personal data; Evolution; Invitations; Paleontology; Photographs; Publication; Requests for reprints; Zoology
    - Cowan, Harry L., 1954 (Box 16)
    - Cowan, Lou N., 1942 (Box 16)
    - Cowen, Robert C., 1960 (Box 16)
    - Cowles, Raymond B., 1958-59 (Box 16)
    - Cowley, W.H., 1965-66 (Box 16)
      deforestation ecology
    - Cox, C.B. (Barry), 1967, 79 (Box 16)
    - Cox, Eric F., 1960 (Box 16)
      All Souls Unitarian Church
    - Cox, M. (Mrs.), 1967, 71 (Box 16)
      Academic Press
    - Cox, Marion, 1965, 68 (Box 16)
    - Coy, Roy E., 1940-41 (Box 16)
    - Coyne, Jerry, 1980 (Box 16)
    - Cracraft, Joel, 1970-74, 1980 (Box 16)
    - Craig, James J., 1968 (Box 16)
    - Craig, T.M., 1962 (Box 16)
    - Cramer, Howard R., 1978-79 (Box 16)
    - Crane, Allison, 1976-78, 81 (Box 16)
      Oxford University Press
    - Crane, E.V., 1960 (Box 16)
    - Crane, Jules M., Jr., 1962 (Box 16)
    - Crank Letters - AAAS Speech, 1959-60 (Box 16)
    - Crausaz, Winston, 1982 (Box 16)
    - Crawford, Victoria, 1975-76 (Box 16)
    - Creation-Science Research Center, 1973 (Box 16)
    - Crisci, Jorge V., 1980 (Box 16)
    - Crist, Raymond E., 1983 (Box 16)
    - Crittendan, Max D., Jr., 1973 (Box 16)
    - Crochet, Jean-Yves, 1979 (Box 16)
    - Crocker, Denton W., 1963 (Box 16)
    - Croizat, Leon, 1959 (Box 16)
      zoogeography
    - Crompton, A. W. (Fuzz), [Alfred Walter], 1970-1971; 20.0 Item(s) (Box 16)
      Museum of Comparative Zoology
      Bibliographical matters -- Greenwood, Peter Humphrey; Bibliographical matters -- Jenkins, Farish A.; Bibliographical matters -- Levi, Herbert Walter; Bibliographical matters -- Williams, Ernest Edward; Biographical and personal data -- Greenwood, Peter Humphrey; Biographical and personal data -- Jenkins, Farish A.; Biographical and personal data -- Levi, Herbert Walter; Biographical and personal data -- Williams, Ernest Edward; Evolution -- Reptiles; Harvard University -- Museum of Comparative Zoology; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Patterson, Bryan; Recommendations; Recommendations -- Williams, Ernest Edward; Requests for reprints
    - Cropp, F.W., 1980, 83 (Box 16)
    - Cross, Ethal F., 1972 (Box 16)
    - Cross, Margaret W., 1975 (Box 16)
    - Cross, Wilbur L., 1927 (Box 16)
    - Crossman, F.J., 1978 (Box 16)
    - Crouch, John, 1976-77 (Box 16)
    - Crowe, John H., 1974 (Box 16)
    - Crowell, Thomas Y., Company, 1961, 70, 72 (Box 16)
    - Crowell-Collier Education Corporation, 1961-62, 64, 67; 2 folders (Box 16)
      Includes: 1962 paper
    - Crowther, Frank H., 1959-60 (Box 16)
    - Cruikshank, Terry, 1965 (Box 17)
    - Crusafont Pairo, Miguel, 1948, 55-83 (Box 17)
    - Cuenot, Claude, 1955-64 (Box 17)
    - Cummings, Philip H., 1941 (Box 17)
      Exhibit at Explorers Club
    - Cunha, A. Brito da, 1954, 78-79, 82 (Box 17)
    - Curle, Richard, 1952 (Box 17)
    - Current (magazine), 1960, 65 (Box 17)
    - Current Anthropology (journal), 1961, 63-65, 67, 72, 75 (Box 17)
    - Curry, H. Donald, 1940 (Box 17)
    - Curtis, Garniss, 1976 (Box 17)
    - Cushing, John E., Jr., 1940 (Box 17)
    - Cushman, Robert A., 1978 (Box 17)
    - Cuthbertson, Stuart, 1969 (Box 17)
    - Cutler, Roger W., Jr., 1968 (Box 17)
    - Cutler, Wolcott, 1939 (Box 17)
      "Lessons in the Mud"
    - D'Orazio, Vincent, 1979 (Box 17)
    - D'Orsi, Josephine M., 1975 (Box 17)
    - Dade, P.H., 1933 (Box 17)
    - Daenzer, Gilbert, 1973 (Box 17)
    - Dagg, Anne, 1965 (Box 17)
    - Daghetto, A., 1961-62 (Box 17)
    - Dahlberg, Albert A., 1942 (Box 17)
    - Dal Piaz, Giorgio, 1932, 35-37, 74 (Box 17)
    - Dalhousie University, 1964 (Box 17)
    - Dall'Asta, E.R., 1968 (Box 17)
    - Dallman, John E., 1962 (Box 17)
    - Dally, W.C., 1942 (Box 17)
    - Daly, Leora, 1937 (Box 17)
    - Damborenea, Susana, 1982 (Box 17)
    - Damon, Paul E., 1968 (Box 17)
    - Dana Club, 1925-26 (Box 17)
    - Dana, E.S., 1926 (Box 17)
    - Dane, Carle H., 1958 (Box 17)
    - Daniel, Joseph C., Jr., 1957 (Box 17)
    - Daniel, Mike J., 1964-65 (Box 17)
    - Danielsen, Teresa L., 1979-80 (Box 17)
    - Danson, Mary, 1977 (Box 17)
    - Darjeeling Club, Ltd., 1977 (Box 17)
    - Dark, Frank J., 1959-60 (Box 17)
    - Darling, Louis (Mrs.), 1960, 62 (Box 17)
    - Darlington, Philip J., Jr., 1939, 58-60, 80 (Box 17)
    - Darmoian, Solak A., 1972 (Box 17)
    - Darnell, James E., 1972-73 (Box 17)
    - Dart, Stephen W., Jr., 1971 (Box 17)
    - Darton, N.H., 1924 (Box 17)
    - Darwin Anniversary Committee, 1956-57 (Box 17)
    - Dashzovy, D., 1965 (Box 17)
    - Dass, Upangshu, 1975 (Box 17)
    - Davenport, Demorest, 1957 (Box 17)
      Selection and Baldwin effect
    - Davenport, Martha K., 1969 (Box 17)
    - Daves, Princkney, 1934 (Box 17)
    - David, Herm., 1960 (Box 17)
      Evolution of the dog
    - David, J.W. Edgeworth, 1931 (Box 17)
    - David, Joseph T., 1941 (Box 17)
    - Davidheiser, Bolton, 1962, 64, 75-79 (Box 17)
    - Davidson, Eugene, 1939 (Box 17)
    - Davie, D.C., 1924 (Box 17)
    - Davies, A. Morley, 1946 (Box 17)
    - Davis, Bernard D., 1963-64, 84 (Box 17)
    - Davis, D. Dwight, 1942, 46-48, 61 (Box 17)
    - Davis, George H., 1975 (Box 17)
    - Davis, H. Brent, 1966 (Box 17)
    - Davis, Louise, 1962 (Box 17)
    - Davis, Marilyn, 1974 (Box 17)
    - Davis, Peter H., 1963 (Box 17)
    - Davis, R.B., 1968 (Box 17)
    - Davis, Watson, 1940 (Box 17)
    - Davis, William B., 1935, 46 (Box 17)
    - Davison, F. Trubee, 1935, 40, 45 (Box 17)
    - Davison, John A., 1980 (Box 17)
    - Davitashvilli, L. A. (Leo Shiovich), 1965-66, 73-75, 77 (Box 17)
    - Davitt Publishing, Inc., 1964 (Box 17)
      Biolog
    - Dawkins, Phyllis L., 1961 (Box 17)
    - Dawson, E.W., 1959 (Box 17)
    - Dawson, Mary R., 1958, 60, 64-66, 70, 72, 74-75, 81-84 (Box 17)
    - Day, John, Company, Inc., 1965 (Box 17)
    - De Camp, L. Sprague, 1948, 54-55, 60, 64-70, 80, 84 (Box 17)
    - De Coninck, L., 1964 (Box 17)
    - De Costa, John, 1964 (Box 17)
    - De Gasparini, Zulma B., 1970 (Box 17)
    - De Golyer, E., 1955 (Box 17)
      History of paleontology in N. America
    - De Haro, Andres, 1970-71 (Box 17)
    - De Koninck, Charles, 1952 (Box 17)
    - De Lanney, Louis E., 1958 (Box 17)
    - De Rochemont, Rudolph, 1954 (Box 17)
      Archeopteryx
    - De Terra, Helmut, 1957 (Box 17)
    - De Wit, J.J. Duyvene, 1964 (Box 17)
    - DeWitt, Dale, 1947 (Box 17)
    - DeYoung, Gary, Jr., 1961, 64, 73-74 (Box 17)
    - Dean, Wynant, 1960 (Box 18)
    - Deane, Martha (Marian Young), 1953 (Box 18)
    - Debenedetti, Don Salvador, 1930 (Box 18)
    - Deboo, Phili B., 1962 (Box 18)
    - Deely, John N., 1966 (Box 18)
    - Deevey, Edward S., Jr., 1940, 65 (Box 18)
    - Dehm, Richard, 1937, 79 (Box 18)
    - Delaware, University of, 1960-65 (Box 18)
    - Delevoryas, T., 1976 (Box 18)
    - Dell Puzzle Publications, 1975 (Box 18)
      origin of word "kangeroo"
    - Dell, R.K., 1968 (Box 18)
    - Delme, R., 1937 (Box 18)
    - Delson, Eric, 1966, 79-80, 83 (Box 18)
    - Demaray, A.E., 1938 (Box 18)
    - Demson, E.V., 1979 (Box 18)
    - Denbrook, Loren, 1935 (Box 18)
    - Denckla, W. Donner, 1966 (Box 18)
    - Denison University, 1963, 65 (Box 18)
    - Denison, Robert H., 1940, 45 (Box 18)
    - Dennes, William R., 1949 (Box 18)
    - Denny, Charles S., 1938 (Box 18)
    - Denny, M., 1974 (Box 18)
    - Dental Cosmos, 1936 (Box 18)
    - Desmond, Thomas C., 1953, 67 (Box 18)
    - Despres, Linda, 1964 (Box 18)
    - Detroit, College of the City of, 1925 (Box 18)
    - Deutsch, Harvey, 1976 (Box 18)
    - Deutsche Akademie der Naturforscher Leopoldina, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Devender, Thomas Van, 1973 (Box 18)
    - Devillers, Charles (or DeVillers), 1952, 65-66 (Box 18)
    - Devlin, Joseph M., 1957 (Box 18)
    - Dice, Lee R., 1931-32, 34, 53 (Box 18)
    - Dick, John, 1975 (Box 18)
    - Dick, Myvanwy M., 1979 (Box 18)
    - Dick-Peddie, William A., 1973 (Box 18)
    - Dickinson College, 1966 (Box 18)
    - Dickinson, Edward C., 1980 (Box 18)
    - Dickinson, J.M., 1940 (Box 18)
    - Dickinson, William R., 1983 (Box 18)
    - Dickson, John, 1941 (Box 18)
    - Dictionary of American Biography, 1941-42, 55, 72 (Box 18)
    - Dictionary of Scientific Biography, 1968, 84 (Box 18)
    - Dictionary of the History of Ideas, 1967 (Box 18)
    - Dietrich, W.O., 1927-34, 37, 59-61 (Box 18)
    - Dietz, David, 1964 (Box 18)
    - Diller, Irene C., 1942 (Box 18)
    - Dillon, Lawrence S., 1966 (Box 18)
    - Diners Club, 1972 (Box 18)
    - Ditfurth, Hoimar v., 1966, 73 (Box 18)
    - Ditman, Richard, 1971 (Box 18)
    - Ditmars, Raymond L., 1940 (Box 18)
    - Dixon, Clara, 1962 (Box 18)
    - Dixon, R.N., 1981 (Box 18)
    - Dobbin, C.E., 1925 (Box 18)
    - Dobzhansky, Theodosius, 1941-1974; 3 folders (Box 18)
      Biographical and personal data; Conferences and symposia; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Dobzhansky, Theodosius. 70th birthday; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- National Medal of Science; Coon, Carleton S.; Drosophila genetics; Evolution; Human genetics -- Race; Mayr, Ernst; Molecular genetics; Paleontology; Philosophy of science--Language of science; Research support; Reviews; Russian politics and science; Sagan, Carl; Teilhard de Chardin, Pierre; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Travel -- South America; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.; World War II -- Impact on science; Zoology
    - Dodd, Elsa, 1941 (Box 18)
    - Dodd, Mead and Co., 1946-48, 50, 57, 61 (Box 18)
    - Dodd, Richard, 1965 (Box 18)
    - Dodson, Edward O., 1974, 81-82 (Box 18)
    - Dodson, Maurice, 1975-76 (Box 18)
    - Doello-Jurado, Martin, 1931, 33, 35, 41, 46 (Box 18)
    - Doetsch, Raymond, 1968 (Box 18)
    - Doggett, Wendy, 1975 (Box 18)
    - Dole, Gertrude, 1962 (Box 18)
    - Dollard, John, 1964 (Box 18)
    - Dollo, L., 1928 (Box 18)
    - Dominion Museum, 1969 (Box 18)
    - Domning, Daryl P., 1980-82 (Box 18)
    - Donaldson, C.S., 1933-34 (Box 18)
    - Dondlinger, Peter T., 1942 (Box 18)
    - Donovan, Alan, 1967 (Box 18)
    - Dooars and Darjeeling Medical Association, 1977 (Box 18)
    - Doolittle, Russell F., 1963, 66 (Box 18)
    - Dorf International, Ltd., 1969 (Box 18)
    - Doria, Vincent, 1952 (Box 18)
    - Dorr, Charles H., 1929 (Box 18)
      Dorr News Service
    - Dorr, John A., Jr., 1957, 69 (Box 18)
    - Dorst, Jean, 1954-55, 57 (Box 18)
    - Doubleday and Company, Inc., 1963, 68, 72 (Box 18)
    - Douglas, James, 1949 (Box 18)
      Am. Instit/Mining and Metallurgical Engineers
    - Doutt, J. Kenneth, 1940, 48 (Box 18)
    - Dover Publications, Inc., 1969, 73 (Box 18)
    - Dover, Cedric, 1952 (Box 18)
    - Down, E.H., 1976 (Box 19)
    - Downs, Theodore, 1960, 62, 65, 68, 70-71, 73-74 (Box 19)
    - Doyle, Gerald A., 1964 (Box 19)
    - Doyle, Winfield G., 1949-51 (Box 19)
    - Drat-Ruszczak, Krystyna, 1975 (Box 19)
    - Dressler, Robert L., 1962 (Box 19)
    - Drexler, R.V., 1959 (Box 19)
    - Drone, Patrick, 1974 (Box 19)
    - Drooger, C.W., 1975 (Box 19)
    - Dryden Press, Inc., 1952 (Box 19)
    - Dryden, Lincoln, 1942, 50 (Box 19)
    - DuBois, Charlotte A., 1973 (Box 19)
    - DuGrenier, Bradford, 1961-62 (Box 19)
    - Duarte, William G., 1970 (Box 19)
    - Dubinin, N.P., 1970, 78 (Box 19)
    - Dubos, Rene, 1964 (Box 19)
    - Duckworth Laboratory, Cambridge University, 1966 (Box 19)
    - Duellman, William E., 1958 (Box 19)
    - Duff, Roger, 1968, 71-72 (Box 19)
      Canterbury Museum, New Zealand
    - Duffield, Richard, 1968 (Box 19)
    - Duke University, 1956, 64-65 (Box 19)
      Symposium
    - Dunbar, Carl O., 1922-1976; 60.0 Item(s) (Box 19)
      American Philosophical Society; Biographical and personal data; Conferences and symposia; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- National Academy of Sciences; Invitations; National Academy of Sciences; Paleontology; Paleontology -- Nomenclature; Photographs; Publication; Recommendations -- Gregory, Joseph T.; Reviews; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Zoology
    - Duncan, Ronald, 1970, 75 (Box 19)
    - Duncan, Winifred, 1953 (Box 19)
    - Dunham, Ethel C., 1961 (Box 19)
    - Dunham, William Huse, 1978 (Box 19)
    - Dunlap, Edgar, 1974-75 (Box 19)
    - Dunlap, Walter M., 1936 (Box 19)
    - Dunn, E.R., 1942, 46 (Box 19)
    - Dunn, Marie W., 1933-34 (Box 19)
    - Durham, University of, 1951 (Box 19)
    - Durning, Edward Wentz, 1964 (Box 19)
    - Durrant, Stephen D., 1937 (Box 19)
    - Dutton, E.P. and Company, Inc., 1966 (Box 19)
    - Dwinedi, M.P., 1969 (Box 19)
    - Dymond, J.R., 1939-40 (Box 19)
      Royal Canadian Institute lecture
    - Dystra, B.S., 1963 (Box 19)
    - Eagan, Mason, 1971 (Box 19)
    - Eagar, R.M.C., 1962, 64 (Box 19)
    - Eaglen, Bob, 1979 (Box 19)
    - Eakin, Richard M., 1973 (Box 19)
    - Earl, Paul, 1956 (Box 19)
      Protozoology
    - Earth Science Reviews/Atlas, 1968-69 (Box 19)
    - Easterla, David A., 1974 (Box 19)
    - Eastern Association of Graduates of the Angle School of Orthodontia, 1926 (Box 19)
    - Eastlake, Mr. and Mrs. William E., 1958-61 (Box 19)
    - Eastman Kodak Co., 1940 (Box 19)
    - Eastman, William B., 1966 (Box 19)
    - Easton, William H., 1942, 74 (Box 19)
      Mendel's experiments w/ hybridization
    - Eaton, T.H., 1967 (Box 19)
    - Eatou, George F., 1925 (Box 19)
    - Eberhart, Bruce, 1966 (Box 19)
    - Eccles, John C., 1964 (Box 19)
    - Echternacht, Arthur C., 1978 (Box 19)
    - Eckel, Edwin B., 1971 (Box 19)
    - Eckhardt, Robert B., 1975 (Box 19)
    - Eckler, Rickey, 1962 (Box 19)
      Extinction
    - Ecology (journal), 1957 (Box 19)
    - Edge, David, 1963 (Box 19)
    - Edinger, Tilly, 1928-29, 33-41, 48-55, 60, 66-67 (Box 19)
      General note
      Contains 1 undated letter from Santa Cecilia signed by a "T.J.E.," most likely not Tilly Edinger.
    - Editorial Revisions, Inc., 1946 (Box 19)
    - Edmund, A. Gordon, 1959, 70 (Box 19)
    - Edsall, John, 1966 (Box 19)
    - Educational Development Center, 1969 (Box 19)
    - Edwards, Dorothy, 1933 (Box 19)
    - Edwards, Paul, 1975 (Box 19)
    - Edwards, W.N., 1948 (Box 19)
    - Efron, Vera, 1947 (Box 19)
    - Egler, Walter Antonio, 1956 (Box 19)
    - Ehrenberg, Kurt, 1936-37, 40, 60, 62, 70, 73 (Box 19)
    - Ehrlich, Paul R., 1963, 67 (Box 19)
    - Eichler, Wolfdietrich, 1963, 1979 (Box 19)
    - Einstein, Albert, 1954 (Box 19)
      Emergency Civil Liberties Committee gala
    - Eisel, Leo M., 1972 (Box 19)
    - Eiseley, Loren C., 1942, 47, 53 (Box 19)
    - Eisenberg, Leon, 1966 (Box 19)
    - Eisenmann, V., 1981 (Box 19)
    - Eisner, W., 1975 (Box 19)
    - Eissler, K.R., 1972-73 (Box 19)
    - Elbert, Samuel H., 1967 (Box 20)
    - Elder, Joseph D., 1962 (Box 20)
    - Elder, William H., 1961 (Box 20)
    - Eldredge, Niles, 1974, 79, 81 (Box 20)
      Cladistics
    - Elephant Interest Group, 1981 (Box 20)
    - Elias, M.K., 1940, 46-47, 50, 52, 55-56, 69 (Box 20)
    - Ellerman, John, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Elliot, David H., 1975 (Box 20)
    - Elliott, Clark A., 1976 (Box 20)
    - Elliott, Edith L., 1926 (Box 20)
    - Elliott, R. John, 1970 (Box 20)
    - Ellis, A.T., 1977 (Box 20)
    - Ellsworth, Heidi, 1969 (Box 20)
    - Ellsworth, Jack, 1962 (Box 20)
    - Ellsworth, Stanley, 1966 (Box 20)
    - Elsevier Scientific Publishing Company, 1967, 79-80 (Box 20)
    - Embree, Lester E., 1982 (Box 20)
    - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 1954 (Box 20)
    - Emerson, Alfred E., 1940, 46, 1960-61, 65, 72 (Box 20)
    - Emlen, John T., 1962 (Box 20)
    - Employees Benefits Program, AMNH, 1959 (Box 20)
    - Enciclopedia Italiana, 1972, 78-79 (Box 20)
    - Enciso, Julian, 1930 (Box 20)
    - Encyclopedia Americana, 1955, 67, 69 (Box 20)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1928, 40, 45-47, 54, 56, 59, 68; 2 folders (Box 20)
      Includes: texts submitted
    - Encyclopedic Dictionary (U.S.S.R.), 1964 (Box 20)
    - Engel, Steven F., 1968 (Box 20)
    - Englander, David A., 1962 (Box 20)
    - Epling, Carl, 1937, 43, 47-50 (Box 20)
    - Erausquin, Jorge, 1938, 53-54 (Box 20)
    - Erben, H. K., 1979 (Box 20)
    - Erickson, Ralph O., 1942-69 (Box 20)
    - Erickson, Rudolph, 1954 (Box 20)
    - Ericson, Edward L., 1975 (Box 20)
    - Eriksen, Lance, 1976 (Box 20)
    - Ernst, Carl H., 1972 (Box 20)
    - Ernst, W. Gary, 1979-81 (Box 20)
    - Errington, Paul L., 1941 (Box 20)
    - Erslev, Allan J., 1972 (Box 20)
    - Erwin, Terry L., 1975 (Box 20)
    - Escalon, Salvador, 1940, 45 (Box 20)
    - Escribano, Virginio, 1983 (Box 20)
    - Espil, Felipe A., 1933 (Box 20)
    - Essig, Nancy, 1970 (Box 20)
    - Estes, Richard D., 1966, 75 (Box 20)
    - Etkin, William, 1963 (Box 20)
    - Eussler, Alex, 1974 (Box 20)
    - Evans, David A., 1970 (Box 20)
    - Evans, Gordon, 1964 (Box 20)
    - Evans, Herbert M., 1942 (Box 20)
    - Evans, Howard E., 1952, 59, 67, 69 (Box 20)
    - Evans, Linda, 1960 (Box 20)
    - Evans, Llewellyn T., 1944 (Box 20)
    - Evans, Thomas H., 1937, 41 (Box 20)
    - Evanstock, Philip, 1960 (Box 20)
    - Everham, Edwin M. III, 1981 (Box 20)
    - Every, Edward F. (Right Rev. Bishop), 1935 (Box 20)
      Attending Marvels
    - Every, R.G., 1972 (Box 20)
    - Evolutionary Biology Committee, 1964 (Box 20)
    - Ewbank, Paul, 1983 (Box 20)
    - Ewen, E., 1971 (Box 20)
    - Ewer, R.F. (Griff), 1962, 69-71, 74 (Box 20)
    - Ewing, Maurice, 1958, 64 (Box 20)
    - Explorer's Club, 1931, 33-45 (Box 20)
    - Eyde, Richard H., 1978 (Box 20)
    - Faber, E.B., 1936 (Box 20)
    - Fagan, J.M., 1948 (Box 20)
    - Fagle, David L., 1962 (Box 20)
    - Fahlbusch, V., 1979 (Box 20)
    - Fairservis, Walter A., Jr., 1966 (Box 20)
    - Falkenbach, C., n.d. (Box 20)
    - Family Coordinator (magazine), 1968 (Box 20)
    - Fan Memorial Institute of Biology, 1933 (Box 20)
    - Fannin, Paul (U.S. Senator), 1968 (Box 20)
    - Farber, Seymour M., 1972-73 (Box 21)
    - Farlow, James O., Jr., 1968, 81 (Box 21)
      K/T boundary
    - Farmer, Helen, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Farner, Donald S., 1976 (Box 21)
    - Farquhar, David M., 1969 (Box 21)
    - Farrand, Max, 1942 (Box 21)
    - Farrell, V.A., 1939 (Box 21)
    - Farrington, Edith, 1939 (Box 21)
    - Farwell, F. Evans, 1976-77 (Box 21)
    - Faulconer, Robert J., 1963 (Box 21)
    - Faunce, Wayne M., 1929, 31-34, 36, 40-42 (Box 21)
      Annual report, AMNH
    - Faure, J.C., 1947 (Box 21)
    - Faus, Russell, 1939 (Box 21)
    - Fay, George E., 1963 (Box 21)
    - Feaver, J. Clayton, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Fechtner, Fredrick R., 1966 (Box 21)
    - Federal Advertising Agency, Inc., 1932 (Box 21)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ of America, 1950 (Box 21)
      Biological Foundations of Ethics Report
    - Federation of American Scientists, 1964 (Box 21)
    - Feduccia, Alan, 1976 (Box 21)
    - Feer, Michael, 1963 (Box 21)
    - Fejos, Paul, 1961-62 (Box 21)
      Wenner-Gren Foundation
    - Feldman, Gabriel E., 1982, 84 (Box 21)
      History of mammalogy
    - Feldman, Rodney M., 1977, 79-82 (Box 21)
      Journal of Paleontology
    - Fell, H. Barry, 1968-69, 71 (Box 21)
    - Fenner, Mildred Sandison, 1963 (Box 21)
    - Fenton, Carroll Lane, 1950 (Box 21)
    - Ferdinand Enke Verlag, 1970 (Box 21)
    - Ference, Michael, 1970 (Box 21)
    - Ferguson, C.W., 1968 (Box 21)
    - Ferguson, E.S., 1966 (Box 21)
    - Fernandez Bueno, Ma. Counsuelo, 1975 (Box 21)
      Mexico City TV show: "Encuentro"
    - Ferrara, Robert P., 1972 (Box 21)
    - Ferril, T.H., 1967 (Box 21)
      Rocky Mountain Herald
    - Ferrin, Mariann, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Ferris, D.H., 1963 (Box 21)
    - Fertig, Daniel S., 1965 (Box 21)
    - Feruglio, Egidio, 1930-32, 34-36, 44 (Box 21)
    - Fesler, Gertrude, 1968 (Box 21)
    - Field Enterprises Education Corporation, 1963 (Box 21)
    - Field Enterprises, Inc., 1957 (Box 21)
    - Field Museum of Natural History, 1934-35 (Box 21)
    - Field, Henry, 1970-71 (Box 21)
    - Fields, Robert W., 1961, 74 (Box 21)
    - Fiennes, Richard N., 1969 (Box 21)
    - Filak, Dolores C., 1958 (Box 21)
    - Filho, Jose Oiticica, 1946 (Box 21)
    - Finck, J.L., 1963 (Box 21)
    - Findley, James S., 1978 (Box 21)
    - Fine, Paul E.M., 1968 (Box 21)
      Pathologies in fossils
    - Fineayson, H.H., 1947 (Box 21)
    - Finger, Frank, 1970 (Box 21)
    - Finger, Ken, 1973 (Box 21)
    - Fink, B. Raymond, 1965 (Box 21)
    - Finlay, John David, 1966 (Box 21)
    - First National City Bank, 1972 (Box 21)
    - Fischer, Gloria J., 1962 (Box 21)
    - Fischer, Med. H., 1971-72 (Box 21)
    - Fish, Gene W., 1940 (Box 21)
    - Fisher, Bruce and Company, 1969 (Box 21)
    - Fisher, Donald W., 1965 (Box 21)
    - Fisher, F.J.F., 1966 (Box 21)
    - Fisher, H. Dean, 1967 (Box 21)
    - Fisher, Harvey I., 1947 (Box 21)
      Statistics
    - Fisher, Joseph L., 1963 (Box 21)
    - Fisher, Robert, 1964 (Box 21)
    - Fisher, Ronald A., 1938 (Box 21)
    - Fisheries Research Board of Canada, 1973 (Box 21)
    - Fiske, Barbara, 1950 (Box 21)
    - Fiske, Dorothy, 1945 (Box 21)
    - Fitch, Walter M., 1977 (Box 21)
    - Fittkau, E.J., 1964-66 (Box 21)
    - Fitzroy, Herbert W.K., 1959-60 (Box 21)
    - Flanagan, Dennis, 1967 (Box 21)
      Scientific American
    - Fleagle, John G., 1981-83 (Box 21)
    - Fleisher, Aaron, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Fleming, Charles A., 1947, 68-71, 76 (Box 21)
    - Fleming, Henry S., 1977-78 (Box 21)
    - Fleming, Phyllis J., 1963 (Box 21)